Nazia Hasan

UI / UX Designer





Nazia Hasan +358465760561 nhasan1987@gmail.com Nazarah @NazarahTheCat Nazia Hasan

About

UI / UX Designer with interest on Developers' Experience, Dashboard Design, Location based services Industrial Machinery Monitoring, Well-being Tech. Have 4+ years' experience in UX Design, an M.Sc. degree with UX major and prior experience in Software Quality Assurance. Detail-oriented and collaborative worker. I am ready to undertake new challenges.

Education

•	2014 - 2018 Tampere University of Technology, Tampere, Finland	Master of Science (Technology) Major: User Experience Thesis: Concept Development and User Experience Measurement of Dipor Dashboard for Monitoring status of Digital Service Development Projects
	2005 - 2010 University of Dhaka, Bangladesh	Bachelor of Science (Hons) Major: Computer Science And Engineering

Work Experience

2011 - 2013

2016 - Present	UI / UX Designer
	Sampo Software Oy,
	Tampere, Finland
	User research, UI wireframe
	design, Usability evaluation,
	web design
	Projects: BikeBox mobile
	app, APInf API Management
	Platform, Saalasti Biomass
	Equipment Monitoring UI.
May 2014 -	Sr. Software Quality
Aug 2014	Assurance Engineer
	Ohon Technologies Ltd.,
	Dhaka, Bangladesh

October 2013 -**Software Business Development Executive,** April 2014

TigerIT Bangladesh Ltd., Dhaka, Bangladesh

Software Quality Assurance **Engineer**

SoftwarePeople Bangladesh Ltd., Dhaka, Bangladesh

Skills



Voluntary Works

- International Tutor (Autumn 2015) and Exchange Students' Tutor (Spring 2016) – Tampere University of Technology, Tampere, Finland
- Volunteer Interaction 2016 Conference by IxDA

Reference

- Jarkko Moilanen, Ph.D +358405359066
- Dr. Heli Väätäjä heli.vaataja@gmail.com
- Jarmo Palviainen jarmo.j.palviainen@gmail.com